Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Sophia. call me.
You do not answer your phone.
Your friend says you don't
go to meetings anymore.
I'm worried about you.
I'm at the observatory tonight.
Please call me back.
Do you ever go skiing?
- Do I ever go skiing?
- Yes.
Because you work in the mountains.
ll mean.
I used to.
but it was ages ago.
- Is everything alright?
- Yes.
Terrible. this.
My men have secured things. You can be
rest assured if they get in the way.
I will do.
- What is it?
- Multiple objects are approaching the earth.
- What kind of objects?
- No idea.
They are approaching at more
than 1000 kilometers per second.
Impossible.
They are slowing down.
Because they entered our atmosphere.
Could it…
be an attack?
Impact in eighty seconds.
Ten seconds left.
Six. five. four. three. two …
Several places have been hit …
but only in certain areas.
it seems.
I want an update every ten minutes
about the affected places.
Hello. sister.
I hope you're unharmed.
I know you don't want to talk …
just send a message
that all is well.
Please.
Pick up. damn it.
Sophia
Why do you keep calling me?
We are not like each other now.
but come to the observatory.
Why?
It's safer.
- Are those things dangerous then?
- I do not know.
Please come here.
Trust me now.
What is going on?
- Do you still have gas in your tank?
- Yes. Now tell me what's up.
- Leave everything behind and come here.
- Why? You are scaring me.
- Sophia. I beg you.
- Okay.
There are already four unknown substances
that have been found.
What causes
the electromagnetic field?
We only know the frequency
and vibration width are constantly increasing.
We also send space probes to
other planets. Is it possible …
that they are here to do research.
Why would they send so many?
And why only to inhabited areas?
Since the first signal.
It took exactly one day.
Yeah so?
They must have made a scan.
Have they mapped the earth?
Do we have to destroy them?
- They could be weapons.
- Take the pictures of Wyoming.
Look. An F-16 has bombed one.
and it survived with no scratches.
- To the station.
- I have no service.
What is that?
The electromagnetic fields
affect the atmosphere.
Colonel. the British government
warns of an attack.
Hello. where are you?
In a traffic jam. I'm stuck.
Listen.
We're being attacked. seek cover.
- Attacked?
- Just search for underground coverage.
- Hurry up.
- I can't go anywhere.
- Sorry to ruin everything.
- That is not true.
- Yes. And you always help me.
- Make sure you go underground.
- I have said so much to you.
- Go underground. Right now.
I would not know where.
We are the contact with our
planes lost. They have crashed.
- Something is happenineg.
- Hello…
Colonel.
What is happening?
No more network
Restore the connection..
Keep all doors closed.
- Is it over?
- That has yet to be seen.
Guys. turn your flashlights off.
We must save the batteries.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm